Guide to the Stanford University, Public Affairs Office, Records of the Vice President
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, 1960-1980; Accession ARCH-1986-033
  - PUBLIC EXERCISES, Committee on, 113, t hru 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - PUBLIC EXERCISES, Committee on, 114, beg. 1/7L (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - PUBLIC INTEREST- Physics (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - PUBLIC RELATIONS- Other Universities (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - PUBLIC RELATIONS- Stanford General, Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - QUAD- beg. 8/73 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - QUESTIONNAIRES (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - RADIO SCIENCE (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - RADIO and TELEVISION (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - RADIO. Television: Asilomar (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - RADVANYI, Janos (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - RAM'S HEAD (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - RECRUITING on Campus (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - RECRUITING on Campus (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - REAGAN, Ronald, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - REGISTRAR'S OFFICE- beg. 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - REGISTRATION (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - REHNQUIST, William, H., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - REINECKE, Edwin (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - RELIGION (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - RESEARCH ADMINISTRATION: f/ l thru Dec, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - RESEARCH ADMINISTRATION: f/2 beg. 1972 ~ (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - RESEARCH ADMINISTRATION: Mailing Lists (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - RESEARCH at Stanford (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - RESEARCH, Classified: John Foster Letter (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - RESEARCH: Cancer (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - RESEARCH CENTER INFORMATION REPORT (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - RESEARCH EXPOSITION (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - RESEARCH: General (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ROSE BOWL 1971: Tickets (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - ROSE BOWL 1971: Activities Schedule (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - ROSE BOWL 1971: Misc (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - ROTARY, San Diego- 1973 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - ROTARY, Sacramento- 1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - ROTC: Controversy Correspondence- Jan. thru Mar. 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - ROTC: April I-IS, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - ROTC: Chronology, Spring 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - ROTC: General 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ROTC: 1971 & 1972-75 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ROTC: 1974-75 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - STANFORD JUDICIAL COUNCIL (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Additional Material, 1956-1980; Accessiion ARCH-1987-078
  Correspondence, minutes, memoranda, reports, speeches, and other records, 1956-1980, generated by Robert M. Rosenzweig, Vice President for Public Affairs, his predecessor Lyle M. Nelson, Director of University Relations, and other staff including Don Carlson. Among the issues covered by these records are athletics, foundations, campus news service, Parents' Day, overseas campuses, Medical Center, minorities, research (recombinent DNA, military), student demonstrations, campus publications, and visitors. This series also includes files of President Richard W. Lyman's speeches.
- Additional Material, 1978-1987; Accession ARCH-1987-079
  This series consists of records pertaining to the proposed Ronald Reagan Presidential Library slated to be built on the Stanford campus. Included are correspondence, reports, committee files, photographs, clippings, and other documents, 1978-1987.
- Additional Material, 1970-1980; Accession ARCH-1991-101
  Correspondence, legal documents, reports, articles, and clippings, 1970-80, regarding the dismissal of Prof. H. Bruce Franklin. Correspondence includes letters from the public, letters by staff to authors of articles, letters accompanying the dispersal of the Decision of the Advisory Board in the Matter of Professor H. Bruce Franklin, 1972, and correspondence regarding the ACLU appeal of 1980.
  - Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-Dec. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1974-79 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Crank letters, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Statement of charges, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hearing brief, University, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Supplemental brief, University (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brief, H. Bruce Franklin (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Amicus Curiae Brief, ACLU, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Board decision, 1972 (photocopy of typescript) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Advisory Board decision, 1972 (newspapers printed version) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Summary of Advisory Board report, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Motion for reconsideration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Declaration of Robert M. Rosenzweig, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Defendant's Motion for Summary Judgment, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Defendant's Motion for Summary Judgment, 1977 – faculty defendants memorandum (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Decision on Motion for Summary judgment, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Appeal, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Information (articles, press releases, etc.), Oct. – Dec. 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Information (articles, press releases, etc.), Jan. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Information (articles, press releases, etc.), Jan. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Information (articles, press releases, etc.), Feb. – Dec. 1972, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - S.U. News Service press releases, 1971-72 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, press releases (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, press releases (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, press releases (Box 3, Folder 4)